AFSCME, District Council 37 Photographs PHOTOS.247
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: DC 37 History, [1946]-[1994].
  - Subseries A: Events, [1946]-1993.
    - Poor People's March, [Jun 1968] (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Demonstration by Judicial Conference Employees (Local 1070), [Jun 26, 1968] (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Lillian Roberts Jail Protest, Dec 1968 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Demonstration for Promotional Opportunities (Local 1549), [May 21, 1969] (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - DC 37 25th Anniversary, [1969] (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Various Gatherings: Fully or Partially Identified, 1950s-1960s (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Demonstrations/Rallies/Campaigns: Unidentified, 1950s-1960s (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Conferences/Meetings/Elections: Unidentified (I), [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Conferences/Meetings/Elections: Unidentified (II), [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Conferences/Meetings/Elections: Unidentified (III), [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Conferences/Meetings/Elections: Unidentified (IV), [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Conferences/Meetings/Elections: Unidentified (V), [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Officers Installations & Local Charters: Unidentified, [1950s-1960s] (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - AFSCME International Convention--Denver, [May 1970] (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Labor-Student Coalition for Peace Anti-War Rally, [May 21, 1970] (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Family Day, [Jun 20, 1970] (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Save Our City Rallies--Albany & New York City, [Apr] 1971 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Pension Strike, Blue Collar Locals, [Jun 7-8, 1971] (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Demonstration in Support of Newark Teachers Union, [Dec 23, 1971] (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Clerical Contract Ratification (Oversize), Jan 4, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Supervising Clerk Exam Prep (Local 1549), [1972] (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Conference of Black Trade Unionists--Chicago, [Sep 1972] (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Brooklyn Museum Unionization Demonstration, [Mar 3, 1974] (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Coney Island Hospital Demonstration (Oversize), May 22, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Model Cities Protest (Local 371), [1974] (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - "Jobs Now" Rallies--Washington, DC, [Apr 1975] (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Local 420 Strike, [Jul-Sep 1976] (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - New York City Fiscal Crisis, [1975-1976] (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Anti-Pornography Rally, [Apr 1977] (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Full Employment Rally, [Sep 7, 1977] (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Conference (Third Annual), [1978] (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Operation Price Watch, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Hugh Carey Rally, [1979] (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - J.P. Stevens Boycott Rally, [1970s] (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Demonstrations/Rallies: Unidentified, [1970s] (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Various Gatherings: Unidentified, [1970s] (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Anti-Draft Rally--Washington, DC, Mar 22, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Solidarity Day and Solidarity Day II, 1981, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Unit Bargaining, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - South African Embassy Protest--Washington, DC, Feb 1985 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Martin Luther King Tribute (Central Labor Council, AFL-CIO), Jan 16, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Local 375 Demonstration Against Contracting Out, [Jul 11, 1986] (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Rally for LTV Steel Mining Company Retirees, [1986?] (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - No Aid to Contras Rally--Washington. DC, Apr 25, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Delegates Meeting, [Dec 1987] (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Dukakis Rally, Oct 21, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Eastern Airlines Strike (DC 37 Support), [Mar 1989] (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Deborah Hospital Tribute, [1980s?] (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Conferences/Gatherings: Identified, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Demonstrations: Unidentified, [1980s] (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Various Gatherings: Unidentified, [1970s-1980s] (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - Bill Clinton Presidential Campaign (Oversize), [1992] (Box XOS001, Folder 1)
    - March on Washington, [Aug] 1993 (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - Demonstrations/Rallies: Unidentified, [1990s] (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - Demonstrations/Rallies: Unidentified (Oversize), [1990s] (Box XOS001, Folder 1)
    - Meetings: Unidentified (Oversize), [1990s] (Box XOS001, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: DC 37 Officers and Staff, 1955-1993.
    - Executive Director: Jerry Wurf (I), 1955-1966, undated (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - Executive Director: Jerry Wurf (II), Undated (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - Executive Director: Jerry Wurf (III), Undated (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - Executive Director: Calogero ("Charlie") Taibi, [1960s] (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - Executive Director: Jerry Wurf and Victor Gotbaum (together), Undated (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - Executive Director: Victor Gotbaum, 1966-1988, undated (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - Executive Director: Stanley Hill, [1988]-1993, undated (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Executive Director: Lillian Roberts, 1972-1979, undated (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Officers, 1948-[1988], undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Former Staff: Identified, 1966-1974, [1966-1986], undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Former Staff: Unidentified, 1964-1979, [1965-1980], undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Subseries C: DC 37 Members, 1956-[1994].
    - Portraits, 1960-[1986], undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Department of Parks, 1956-1966, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Department of Parks (oversize), Undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Members on the Job: Climbers and Pruners (Local 1506), [1956] (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Members on the Job, 1959-1966, [1960-1965] (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Members on the Job, [1950s-1960s] (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Members on the Job, 1974-1979, [1970s] (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Members on the Job: Police Department Aides and Technicians, [1974]-1982, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Members on the Job, 1980, [1980s-1994] (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Retirees Association: Rallies, 1985, [1980s] (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: AFSCME, [1955]-1990.
    - Arnold Zander, [1950s-1960s] (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - District Council 36 (New Jersey), [Jan 25, 1955] (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - General Photographs, 1962-1966, [1950s-1960s] (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - New York State Legislative Committee, 1964, [1960s] (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - District Council 50 (New York State), [1960s] (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Gerald McEntee, 1988-1990, undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Other Individuals/Organizations, 1956-1989.
    - Civil Rights Leaders, 1963-1966, [1959-1995] (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Coalition of Labor Union Women, [1980s] (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - David Dinkins, 1985, undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Labor Leaders, 1961-1988, undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - New York Area Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador, 1986-1988, undated (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - New York Area Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador (Oversize), 1986, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - New York City/New York State Politicians, 1956-[1990], undated (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Politicians, Other, 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt, [Aug 1959] (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - United Farm Workers, [1970s], 1986 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Subseries F: Portraits: Partial or No Identification, 1948-1987.
    - Individuals: Identified, 1986, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Individuals: Unidentified, Undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Groups: Persons or Group Identified, 1948-1987, undated (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Groups: Persons or Group Identified (Oversize), 1961-1969 (Box XOS001, Folder 1)
    - Groups: Unidentified (I), Undated (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Groups: Unidentified (II), Undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Series IV: DC 37 Subject Files, 1957-2000.
  - College of New Rochelle, 1973-1992, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Community Association (Images Taken for Newsletter), 1986-1998, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - DC 37 Headquarters/ Med Plan Lobby, 1957, undated (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Education, 1963-1979, [1960s-1970s] (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Education, 1980-1993, [1980s-1990s] (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Everyday Heroes, Undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Health and Security, 1984-1988, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - High School Equivalency Training Program, 1969, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Housing Committee, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian and Gay Issues Committee (Images Taken for Newsletter), 2000, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Med Plan (Images Taken for Newsletter), 1975-1985, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Municipal Employees Legal Services (MELS), 1974, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (Images Taken for Newsletter), Undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Nurses' Aides Upgrading Program, 1967-1972, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, 1967, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Pension Counseling, 1964-1966, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Political Action and Legislative Department/Political Action Committee (Images Taken for PAC Newsletter), 1985-1998, undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE)/Images Taken for PEOPLE Newsletter, 1978-1990, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL), 1987-1991, undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL), 1992-1996 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL), Undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Quality of Work Life Committee (QWL): Images Used in QWL Booklet, 1982-1989, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Retirees Association (Images Taken for "The Active Retiree" Newsletter), 1979-2000, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Safety, 1974-1980, undated (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Shop Steward Training, Undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Summer Camp, 1963-1996, undated (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Travel, 1960, 1974, [1960s-1970s] (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Women's Committee, 1982-1984, undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Retirees Meeting, Demonstration against "City Time", 2010 (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 18)
- Series V: General Subject Files, 1966-1989.
  - Africa, 1973, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Albany, 1990-1991, undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Animals, 1973-1974, undated (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Cemetery, Undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Children, 1973-1991, undated (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Disabled, 1981-1985, undated (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Industrial & Commercial Incentive Board, 1980-1988, undated (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - New York City History, 1982, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - New York City Scenes by Photographer Peter Fink, [1967] (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Production Stills: Labor-Related Films, Undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - PEP Photographs, 1963, 1977, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 4)
  - News, Events, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 018, Folder 17)
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, [1958]-[2001].
  - Subseries A: Numbered Contact Sheets, [1982]-[2000]
    - [DC] 4312 - 4390, Jun-Aug 1982, [1982] (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - [DC] 4391 - 4441, Aug-Sep 1982, [1982] (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - [DC] 4442 - 4491, Oct-Nov 1982, [1982] (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - [DC] 4492 - 4533, Nov-Dec 1992, [1982] (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - [DC] 4534 - 4608, Dec 1982-Jan 1983, [1982-1983] (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - [DC] 4609 - 4697, Feb-Apr 1983, [1983] (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - [DC] 4699 - 4738, Apr-May 1983, [1983] (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - [DC] 4740 - 4775, May-Jun 1983, [1983] (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - [DC] 4776 - 4836, Jun-Aug 1983, [1983] (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - [DC] 4837 - 4889, Sep-Oct 1983, [1983] (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 4890 - 4956, Oct-Nov 1983, [1983] (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 4957 - 5009, Jan-[Mar] 1984, [1984] (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 5010 - 5040, [Mar-May 1984] (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 5041 - 5085, [Mar-May 1984] (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 5086 - 5141, [May-Jul 1984] (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 5142 - 5201, [Jul-Nov 1984] (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 5202 - 5244, circa Nov 1984 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 5245 - 5279, [Nov 1984-Jan 1985] (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 5281 - 5318, [Jan-Mar 1985] (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 5319 - 5373, [Mar-Apr 1985] (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 5374 - 5434, [Apr-Jun 1985] (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 5435 - 5495, [1985] (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 5496 - 5570, [1985-Jan 1986] (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 5571 - 5640, [Jan-May 1986] (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 5641 - 5685, circa May 1986 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 5686 - 5736, [May-Aug 1986] (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 5737 - 5789, [Aug-Dec 1986] (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 5790 - 5837, [Dec 1986-1987] (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 5838 - 5881, [1987] (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 5882 - 6061, [1987] (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 6062 - 6096, circa Sep 1987 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 6097 - 7043, [Sep-Nov 1987] (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 7044 - 7091, [Nov 1987-Jan 1988] (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 7092 - 8032, [Jan-Feb 1988] (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 8034 - 8051, [Mar 1988] (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 8053 - 8090, [Mar-Apr 1988] (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 8092 - 8139, [May-Jun 1988] (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 8140 - 8165, [Jun-Sep 1988] (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 8166 - 8202, [Sep-Oct 1988] (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 8203 - 8245, [Oct-Nov 1988] (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 8246 - 8279, [Dec 1988-Jan 1989] (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 8280 - 8309, [Jan-Feb 1989] (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 8310 - 8338, [Feb-Apr 1989] (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 8339 - 8370, [Apr-May 1989] (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 8371 - 8419, [May-Jun 1989] (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 8421 - 8436, [Jun-Sep 1989] (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - [DC] 8437 - 8464, [Sep-Oct 1989] (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - [DC] 8465 - 8506, [Oct 1989] (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - [DC] 8507 - 8554, [Oct 1989-Jan 1990] (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - [DC] 8556 - 8605, [1990] (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - [DC] 8606 - 8634, [1990] (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 8635 - 8675, [1990] (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 8676 - 8727, [1990] (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 8728 - 8763, [1990] (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 8764 - 8796, [1990] (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 8797 - 8844, circa 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 8845 - 8872, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 8873 - 8912, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 8913 - 8950, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 8951 - 8997, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 8999 - 9047, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 9048 - 9098, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 9100 - 9151, [1991] (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - [DC] 9152 - 9204, [1991-1992] (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - [DC] 9205 - 9240, Jan- [Mar] 1992 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - [DC] 9241 - 9321, circa Jan-Apr 1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 9322 - 9355, [1992] (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 9356 - 9386, circa Apr-Jul 1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 9387 - 9429, [1992] (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 9430 - 9476, [1992] (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 9478 - 9529, [1992] (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 9530 - 9575, [1992-1993] (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 9576 - 9621, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 9622 - 9669, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 9670 - 9702, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 9703 - 9745, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 9746 - 9785, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 9786 - 9836, [1993] (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - [DC] 9837 - 9897, [1993-Feb 1994] (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - [DC] 9898 - 9938, circa Feb 1994 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - [DC] 9939 - 9972, [1994] (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 9973 - 10011, [1994] (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 10013 - 10060, [1994] (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 10064 - 10101, [1994] (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 10102 - 10149, Nov-Dec 1994,[1994-Jan 1995] (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 10150 - 10180, Mar 1995,[1995] (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 10181 - 10224, Feb 1995,[1995] (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 10225 - 10251, circa Jul 1995 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 10252 - 10275, [Jul-Aug 1995] (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 10277 - 10300, Aug 1995,[1995] (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - [DC] 10301 - 10359, [1995] (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 10360 - 10388, circa Feb 1996 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - [DC] 10389 - 10422, [1996] (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - [DC] 10423 - 10487, [1996] (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - [DC] 10488 - 10539, [1996] (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - [DC] 10540 - 10595, Nov 1996,[1996-Feb 1997] (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - [DC] 10596 - 10650, Feb 1997,[1997] (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - [DC] 10651 - 10716, [1997] (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - [DC] 10717 - 10765, circa Oct 1997 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - [DC] 10767 - 10828, [Oct-Dec 1997] (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - [DC] 10830 - 10883, Jan-Feb 1998 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - [DC] 10884 - 10943, Feb-Apr 1998 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - [DC] 10945 - 11012, May-Aug 1998 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - [DC] 11015 - 11068, Aug-Nov 1998,[1998] (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - [DC] 11069 - 11137, Dec 1998-Mar 1999 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - [DC] 11138 - 11203, Mar-Aug 1999 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - [DC ]11204 - 11253, Aug 1999-Feb 2000 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - [DC] 11254 - 11266, [Feb-Apr 2000] (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Public Employee Press Contact Sheets, [1967]-[2001]
    - Vol. 8 No. 4 Issue Date: Mar 29, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Vol. 8 Nos. 6-10 Issue Dates: May-Aug 1967 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Vol. 8 Nos. 11-13 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1967 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Vol. 8 No. 14-[16] Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1967 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Vol. 9 Nos. 1-3 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1968 (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Vol. 9 Nos. 4-6 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1968 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Vol. 9 Nos. 7-8 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 9 Nos. 9-14 Issue Dates: Sep-Dec 1968 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 10 Nos. 1-4 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1969 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 10 Nos. 5-7 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1969 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 10 Nos. 8-10 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1969 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 10 Nos. 11-14 Issue Dates: Sep-Nov 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 10 No. 15-Vol. 11 No. 2 Issue Dates: Dec 1969-Jan 1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 11 Nos. 3-4 Issue Dates: Feb-Mar 1970 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 11 Nos. 5-7 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1970 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 11 Nos. 8-9 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1970 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 11 Nos. 10-11 Issue Dates: Aug-Sep 1970 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 11 Nos. 12-14 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1970 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 11 No. 15-Vol. 12 No. 4 Issue Dates: Dec 1970-Mar 1971 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 12 Nos. 5-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Aug 1971 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 12 Nos. 12-14 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 12 No. 15-Vol. 13 No. 1 Issue Dates: Nov 1971-Jan 1972 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 13 Nos. 2-7 Issue Dates: Feb-Apr 1972 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 13 Nos. 8-11 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1972 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Vol. 13 Nos. 12-16 Issue Dates: Jul-Sep 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 13 Nos. 17-22 Issue Dates: Oct-Dec 1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 1-3 Issue Dates: Jan-Feb 1973 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 4-8 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 9-12 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1973 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 13-14 Issue Dates: Jul-Aug 1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 15-18 Issue Date: Sep-Oct 1973 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 14 Nos. 19-23 Issue Date: Nov-Dec 1973 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 15 Nos. 1-4 Issue Date: Jan-Mar 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 15 Nos. 5-9 Issue Date: Apr-May 1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 15 Nos. 10-13 Issue Date: Jun-Jul 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 15 Nos. 14-20 Issue Date: Aug-Nov 1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 15 No. 21-Vol. 16 No. 6 Issue Date: Dec 1974-Mar 1975 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 16 Nos. 7-13 Issue Date: Apr-Jul 1975 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 16 Nos. 14-20 Issue Date: Aug-Nov 1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 16 No. 21-Vol. 17 No. 4 Issue Date: Dec 1975-Feb 1976 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 17 Nos. 5-10 Issue Date: Mar-May 1976 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 17 Nos. 11-16 Issue Date: Jun-Sep 1976 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Vol. 17 No. 17-Vol. 18 No. 2 Issue Date: Oct 1976-Jan 1977 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Vol. 18 Nos. 3-8 Issue Dates: Feb-Apr 1977 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Vol. 18 Nos. 9-13 Issue Dates: May-Jul 1977 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 18 Nos. 14-21 Issue Dates: Aug-Dec 1977 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 19 Nos. 1-6 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 19 Nos. 7-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 19 Nos. 12-17 Issue Dates: Jul-Oct 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 19 Nos. 18-22 Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1978 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 20 Nos. 1-5 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1979 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 20 Nos. 6-9 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 20 Nos. 10-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 20 Nos. 15-21 Issue Dates: Sep-Dec 1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 21 Nos. 1-4 Issue Dates: Jan-Feb 1980 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 21 Nos. 5-10 Issue Dates: Mar-May 1980 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 21 Nos. 11-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1980 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 21 Nos. 15-23 Issue Dates: Aug-Dec 1980 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 22 Nos. 1-7 Issue Dates: Jan-Apr 1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 22 Nos. 8-9 Issue Dates: May 1981 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 22 Nos. 10-12 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1981 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 22 Nos. 13-14 Issue Dates: Aug-Sep 1981 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Vol. 22 Nos. 15-19 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 22 No. 20-Vol. 23 No. 3 Issue Dates: Dec 1981-Feb 1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 23 Nos. 4-10 Issue Dates: Mar-May 1982 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 23 Nos. 11-14 Issue Dates: Jun-Aug 1982 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 23 Nos. 15-18 Issue Dates: Sep-Oct 1982 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 23 Nos. 19-22 Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 24 Nos. 1-5 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 24 Nos. 6-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 24 Nos. 12-17 Issue Dates: Jul-Oct 1983 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 24 No. 18-Vol. 25 No. 1 Issue Dates: Nov 1983-Jan 1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 25 Nos. 2-6 Issue Dates: Feb-Apr 1984 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 25 Nos. 7-11 Issue Dates: Apr-Jun 1984 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 25 Nos. 12-15 Issue Dates: Jul-Sep 1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 25 Nos. 16-18 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 25 Nos. 19-20 Issue Dates: Dec 1984 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 26 Nos. 1-3 Issue Dates: Jan-Feb 1985 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 26 Nos. 4-7 Issue Dates: Mar-Apr 1985 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 26 Nos. 8-11 Issue Dates: May-Jun 1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Vol. 26 Nos. 12-15 Issue Dates: Jul-Sep 1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Vol. 26 Nos. 16-21 Issue Dates: Oct-Dec 1985 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Vol. 27 Nos. 1-5 Issue Dates: Jan-Mar 1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Vol. 27 Nos. 6-10 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Vol. 27 Nos. 11-16 Issue Dates: Jun-Sep 1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Vol. 27 Nos. 17-20 Issue Dates: Oct-Nov 1986 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Vol. 27 No. 21-Vol. 28 No. 1 Issue Dates: Dec 1986-Jan 1987 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 2-5 Issue Dates: Feb-Mar 1987 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 6-9 Issue Dates: Apr-May 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 10-12 Issue Dates: Jun-Jul 1987 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 13-15 Issue Dates: Aug-Sep 1987 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 16-18 Issue Dates: Oct 1987 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Vol. 28 Nos. 19-22 Issue Dates: Nov-Dec 1987 (Box 40, Folder 14)